<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Game Review</title>
    <link>https://sergio-2004.github.io/game_review/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Game Review</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 17:56:14 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sergio-2004.github.io/game_review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Gameplay</title>
      <link>https://sergio-2004.github.io/game_review/posts/cyberpunk_2077/page2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 17:56:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sergio-2004.github.io/game_review/posts/cyberpunk_2077/page2/</guid>
      <description>Cyberpunk 2077, developed by CD Projekt Red, presents a vast and immersive gameplay experience set in a sprawling open-world dystopia. The gameplay centers on V, a mercenary navigating the neon-lit city of Night City, and offers a diverse range of gameplay elements.
The game provides a choice-driven narrative, allowing players to shape their own path through the story. Choices made throughout the game affect character relationships, story outcomes, and the overall atmosphere of Night City, reflecting the essence of the cyberpunk genre.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cyberpunk 2077&lt;/em&gt;, developed by &lt;strong&gt;CD Projekt Red&lt;/strong&gt;, presents a vast and immersive gameplay experience set in a sprawling open-world dystopia. The gameplay centers on V, a mercenary navigating the neon-lit city of Night City, and offers a diverse range of gameplay elements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The game provides a choice-driven narrative, allowing players to shape their own path through the story. Choices made throughout the game affect character relationships, story outcomes, and the overall atmosphere of Night City, reflecting the essence of the cyberpunk genre.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Combat in &lt;em&gt;Cyberpunk 2077&lt;/em&gt; is dynamic and engaging, offering a mix of gunplay, melee combat, and hacking abilities. Players can choose from an extensive array of cybernetic enhancements, skills, and weaponry to suit their preferred playstyle. The inclusion of a deep skill tree and upgrade system provides ample room for customization and growth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The open-world design allows for exploration and interaction with a vast urban landscape. Players can engage in side missions, activities, and immerse themselves in the intricate world of Night City. The visual and auditory aspects of the game are stunning, enhancing the cyberpunk atmosphere with a detailed and futuristic aesthetic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, upon its release, the game faced technical issues and performance limitations, particularly on older console systems. Despite this, the core gameplay experience remains captivating, offering an expansive, choice-rich adventure in a futuristic world that&amp;rsquo;s as beautiful as it is brutal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34; width: 800px; margin-left: 150px;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://sergio-2004.github.io/game_review/images/cp3.png&#34;
       alt=cp3
       width=&#34;500&#34;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plot</title>
      <link>https://sergio-2004.github.io/game_review/posts/cyberpunk_2077/page1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 17:56:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sergio-2004.github.io/game_review/posts/cyberpunk_2077/page1/</guid>
      <description>Cyberpunk 2077 is an ambitious open-world action role-playing video game set in a dystopian future. The game is developed by CD Projekt Red and set in the bustling and technologically advanced Night City, a metropolis obsessed with power, glamour, and cybernetic enhancements. The narrative centers on V, a mercenary striving for fame and fortune, embarking on a mission to secure a prototype immortality chip.
The game unfolds in a nonlinear manner, influenced by player choices and actions, leading to multiple potential endings.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cyberpunk 2077&lt;/em&gt; is an ambitious open-world action role-playing video game set in a dystopian future. The game is developed by &lt;strong&gt;CD Projekt Red&lt;/strong&gt; and set in the bustling and technologically advanced Night City, a metropolis obsessed with power, glamour, and cybernetic enhancements. The narrative centers on V, a mercenary striving for fame and fortune, embarking on a mission to secure a prototype immortality chip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The game unfolds in a nonlinear manner, influenced by player choices and actions, leading to multiple potential endings. As V navigates the complex societal structure and underworld of Night City, they encounter a range of characters, each with their own motivations and agendas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The plot delves deep into themes of identity, transhumanism, corporate greed, and the consequences of one&amp;rsquo;s choices. Players face moral dilemmas, forging alliances and rivalries, ultimately impacting the outcome of their journey and the fate of Night City.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite facing some technical issues upon its initial release, &lt;em&gt;Cyberpunk 2077&lt;/em&gt; remains a compelling narrative-driven experience with a richly detailed world and intricate storytelling, immersing players in a gritty, neon-lit future ripe with danger and intrigue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34; width: 800px; margin-left: 150px;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://sergio-2004.github.io/game_review/images/cp2.png&#34;
       alt=cp2
       width=&#34;500&#34;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gameplay</title>
      <link>https://sergio-2004.github.io/game_review/posts/hades/page2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 17:55:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sergio-2004.github.io/game_review/posts/hades/page2/</guid>
      <description>Hades, developed by Supergiant Games, is a tour de force in the realm of action rogue-like gameplay. The player takes on the role of Zagreus, the son of Hades, navigating through the intricacies of the Underworld in a bid to escape to the surface. The gameplay is fast-paced and highly engaging, featuring a mix of isometric combat and dungeon-crawling elements.
Combat is the highlight, featuring an array of weapons, each with distinct playstyles and upgrade paths.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hades&lt;/em&gt;, developed by &lt;strong&gt;Supergiant Games&lt;/strong&gt;, is a tour de force in the realm of action rogue-like gameplay. The player takes on the role of Zagreus, the son of Hades, navigating through the intricacies of the Underworld in a bid to escape to the surface. The gameplay is fast-paced and highly engaging, featuring a mix of isometric combat and dungeon-crawling elements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Combat is the highlight, featuring an array of weapons, each with distinct playstyles and upgrade paths. The game keeps players on their toes, as they battle a multitude of enemies, each requiring unique strategies to defeat. The fluidity of combat, combined with the beautifully animated attacks and dodges, makes for an exhilarating experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A key aspect is the boon system, where Zagreus receives aid from Olympian gods, enhancing abilities and altering gameplay. The interactions with the gods present a strategic layer, as players choose the boon that aligns with their playstyle or current needs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The rogue-like nature of the game ensures that no two runs are the same. Permadeath is a constant companion, adding an element of challenge and encouraging players to experiment and adapt. The game rewards persistence and skillful gameplay, providing a sense of accomplishment with each successful escape attempt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The progression system is well-designed, allowing players to unlock permanent upgrades, new weapons, and delve deeper into the rich narrative. Overall, &lt;em&gt;Hades&lt;/em&gt; seamlessly weaves together compelling gameplay, stunning visuals, and an engaging story, making it a must-play for fans of the rogue-like genre.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34; width: 800px; margin-left: 150px;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://sergio-2004.github.io/game_review/images/hades3.png&#34;
       alt=hades3
       width=&#34;500&#34;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plot</title>
      <link>https://sergio-2004.github.io/game_review/posts/hades/page1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 17:55:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sergio-2004.github.io/game_review/posts/hades/page1/</guid>
      <description>Hades, an action-packed rogue-like video game developed by Supergiant Games, plunges players into the depths of Greek mythology. The story centers on Zagreus, the son of Hades, as he embarks on a relentless quest to escape the Underworld and reach the surface to reunite with his mother, Persephone.
Set in the beautifully designed realm of the Underworld, the game offers an engaging narrative that evolves with each escape attempt. As Zagreus battles his way through hordes of mythical creatures and challenges, players uncover hidden secrets, forge alliances with gods and spirits, and confront their own family&amp;rsquo;s complex dynamics.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hades&lt;/em&gt;, an action-packed rogue-like video game developed by &lt;strong&gt;Supergiant Games&lt;/strong&gt;, plunges players into the depths of Greek mythology. The story centers on Zagreus, the son of Hades, as he embarks on a relentless quest to escape the Underworld and reach the surface to reunite with his mother, Persephone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set in the beautifully designed realm of the Underworld, the game offers an engaging narrative that evolves with each escape attempt. As Zagreus battles his way through hordes of mythical creatures and challenges, players uncover hidden secrets, forge alliances with gods and spirits, and confront their own family&amp;rsquo;s complex dynamics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The plot is intricately woven, revealing the fractured relationships among the Olympian gods and shedding light on Zagreus&amp;rsquo; determination to discover the truth about his lineage. The interactions with various characters, including the witty conversations with Olympian deities, add depth to the storytelling, making it a delightful experience for players.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What sets &lt;em&gt;Hades&lt;/em&gt; apart is its unique approach to storytelling through repeated gameplay attempts, creating a sense of progress and character development with every escape, accompanied by a diverse array of weapons, abilities, and upgrades. The plot&amp;rsquo;s evolution with each run is masterfully crafted, enticing players to persistently challenge the Underworld and unravel the compelling narrative at its core.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34; width: 800px; margin-left: 150px;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://sergio-2004.github.io/game_review/images/hades2.png&#34;
       alt=hades2
       width=&#34;500&#34;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gameplay</title>
      <link>https://sergio-2004.github.io/game_review/posts/baldurs-gate-3/page2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 17:55:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sergio-2004.github.io/game_review/posts/baldurs-gate-3/page2/</guid>
      <description>Baldur&amp;rsquo;s Gate 3, developed by Larian Studios, delivers a rich and enthralling gameplay experience steeped in the classic Dungeons &amp;amp; Dragons universe. The game is a blend of captivating storytelling, strategic turn-based combat, and intricate decision-making.
The gameplay begins with players creating a character from various races, classes, and backgrounds, allowing for a highly customized role-playing experience. The narrative is deeply immersive, filled with intriguing characters, moral quandaries, and a well-crafted world.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Baldur&amp;rsquo;s Gate 3&lt;/em&gt;, developed by &lt;strong&gt;Larian Studios&lt;/strong&gt;, delivers a rich and enthralling gameplay experience steeped in the classic Dungeons &amp;amp; Dragons universe. The game is a blend of captivating storytelling, strategic turn-based combat, and intricate decision-making.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The gameplay begins with players creating a character from various races, classes, and backgrounds, allowing for a highly customized role-playing experience. The narrative is deeply immersive, filled with intriguing characters, moral quandaries, and a well-crafted world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The turn-based combat system is a standout feature, providing strategic depth and requiring players to consider positioning, abilities, and environmental factors. The use of D&amp;amp;D 5th Edition rules enhances the authenticity of the combat, making it a treat for fans of the tabletop game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The extensive dialogue system allows players to interact with non-player characters, shape alliances, and influence the story&amp;rsquo;s direction. Choices made in dialogue can have profound effects on the plot, encouraging multiple playthroughs to explore various narrative paths.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Exploration is key, and the game boasts an expansive and meticulously crafted world to discover. The attention to detail in both environments and character design is remarkable, adding to the overall immersion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the game is in early access, it already showcases a promising foundation for what is likely to be an epic role-playing experience. Despite some bugs and incomplete features, &lt;em&gt;Baldur&amp;rsquo;s Gate 3&lt;/em&gt; promises an exciting journey through a beautifully realized fantasy world, making it a must-play for RPG enthusiasts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34; width: 800px; margin-left: 150px;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://sergio-2004.github.io/game_review/images/bg3.png&#34;
       alt=bg3
       width=&#34;500&#34;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plot</title>
      <link>https://sergio-2004.github.io/game_review/posts/baldurs-gate-3/page1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 17:55:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sergio-2004.github.io/game_review/posts/baldurs-gate-3/page1/</guid>
      <description>Baldur&amp;rsquo;s Gate 3 transports players into a captivating fantasy realm where chaos reigns and dark forces threaten existence. Developed by Larian Studios, this role-playing video game is a continuation of the iconic Baldur&amp;rsquo;s Gate series. The plot revolves around the city of Baldur&amp;rsquo;s Gate, where a sinister, mind-altering parasite known as the Illithid tadpole infects the player character and several others.
Players find themselves entangled in a struggle against both the malevolent Illithids and the struggles within themselves as the tadpole&amp;rsquo;s influence grows.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Baldur&amp;rsquo;s Gate 3&lt;/em&gt; transports players into a captivating fantasy realm where chaos reigns and dark forces threaten existence. Developed by &lt;strong&gt;Larian Studios&lt;/strong&gt;, this role-playing video game is a continuation of the iconic &lt;em&gt;Baldur&amp;rsquo;s Gate&lt;/em&gt; series. The plot revolves around the city of Baldur&amp;rsquo;s Gate, where a sinister, mind-altering parasite known as the Illithid tadpole infects the player character and several others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Players find themselves entangled in a struggle against both the malevolent Illithids and the struggles within themselves as the tadpole&amp;rsquo;s influence grows. The narrative unfolds through a series of quests and decisions, echoing the traditional Dungeons &amp;amp; Dragons role-playing experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The game is known for its branching storylines, driven by player choices and character interactions. As the infected protagonist, players must grapple with ethical dilemmas and moral choices that can shape the course of the story, leading to multiple possible outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The plot is layered with intricate lore, captivating characters, and the quintessential elements of high fantasy, including magic, mythical creatures, and epic battles. &lt;em&gt;Baldur&amp;rsquo;s Gate 3&lt;/em&gt; is a thrilling journey through a meticulously crafted world, offering a complex narrative that keeps players engaged and eager to uncover the mysteries that lie within this extraordinary realm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34; width: 800px; margin-left: 150px;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;https://sergio-2004.github.io/game_review/images/bg2.png&#34;
       alt=bg2
       width=&#34;500&#34;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homepage</title>
      <link>https://sergio-2004.github.io/game_review/homepage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 16:31:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sergio-2004.github.io/game_review/homepage/</guid>
      <description>Site Summary In this site you will be encountering three different sections, each one of them will have a page with a brief intro into their Plot and another one about their Gameplay.
Cyberpunk 2077 A shooter with RPG mechanics developed by CD Project Red, wich takes place in a distopian world in the near future.
Hades A frenetic RogueLight game with isometric view developed by Supergiant Games, wich is inspired in ancient Greek mitology.</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;site-summary&#34;&gt;Site Summary&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this site you will be encountering three different sections, each one of them will have a page with a brief intro into their &lt;em&gt;Plot&lt;/em&gt; and another one about their &lt;em&gt;Gameplay&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;hahahugoshortcode6s0hbhbgame_reviewpostscyberpunk_2077&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sergio-2004.github.io/game_review/game_review/posts/cyberpunk_2077&#34;&gt;&lt;div&gt;
  &lt;div style=&#34;width: 50px; float: left;&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;https://sergio-2004.github.io/game_review/images/cp_icon.png&#34;
       alt=cyberpunk_2077
       width=&#34;50px&#34;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div style=&#34;float: left;&#34;&gt;
    Cyberpunk 2077
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A shooter with RPG mechanics developed by &lt;strong&gt;CD Project Red&lt;/strong&gt;, wich takes place in a distopian world in the near future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;hahahugoshortcode6s1hbhbgame_reviewpostshades&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sergio-2004.github.io/game_review/game_review/posts/hades&#34;&gt;&lt;div&gt;
  &lt;div style=&#34;width: 50px; float: left;&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;https://sergio-2004.github.io/game_review/images/hades_icon.png&#34;
       alt=hades
       width=&#34;50px&#34;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div style=&#34;float: left;&#34;&gt;
    Hades
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A frenetic RogueLight game with isometric view developed by &lt;strong&gt;Supergiant Games&lt;/strong&gt;, wich is inspired in ancient Greek mitology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;hahahugoshortcode6s2hbhbgame_reviewpostsbaldurs-gate-3&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sergio-2004.github.io/game_review/game_review/posts/baldurs-gate-3&#34;&gt;&lt;div&gt;
  &lt;div style=&#34;width: 50px; float: left;&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;https://sergio-2004.github.io/game_review/images/bg_icon.png&#34;
       alt=baldur&amp;#39;s_gate
       width=&#34;50px&#34;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div style=&#34;float: left;&#34;&gt;
    Baldur&amp;#39;s gate 3
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A RPG with mechanics of TTRPGs, in this case the 5ยบ edition of Dungeons and Dragons, developed by &lt;strong&gt;Larian Studios&lt;/strong&gt; and takes our group of adventurers throw the Sword Coast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
